Contact

01010483839 (Mobile) ahmedelsyd5@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ahmedhindi-358a77123 (LinkedIn) ahmedhindi.medium.com/ (Blog)

Top Skills

Python

Machine Learning

Data Science

Languages

English (Professional Working)

Arabic (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Applied Data Science with Python Specialization

The Data Scientist's Toolbox

Applied Plotting, Charting & Data
Representation in Python

Introduction to Probability and Data
Applied Text Mining in Python

Ahmed Hindi

Senior Machine Learning Engineer at Indeed.com Cairo

Summary

Data Scientist familiar with gathering, cleaning, and organizing data for use by technical and non-technical personnel. Due to working for five years on Upwork, I have experience working with people from different backgrounds, communicating the data at many levels of abstraction dealing with tech and non-tech clients. And during the five years, I was able to maintain a perfect record by finishing all projects successfully. The wide range and variation of projects allowed me to be adaptive, flexible, and efficient at adopting new technologies and getting up to speed in no time, and that's my most valuable asset. I find a way to get things done.

Experience

Indeed.com
Senior Machine Learning Engineer
August 2021 - Present (5 months)

Upwork
Data Scientist/ Analyst
October 2016 - Present (5 years 3 months)
https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~01a5e81e04f550d5b5

Education

coursera

data science · (2016 - 2017)